egypttoday.com 2016-12-11

# Privacy Policy/ToS | Egypt Today

****  
Egypt Today knows that you care how information about you is used` and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) explains Egypt   Today treatment of information that we collect when you are on our website located at Egypt Today.com (the “Site”) and when you use our products and services (collectively, the ” Service”). By using the Service, you are accepting the practices described here. This Policy does not apply to the practices of other divisions of Egypt Today (“Egypt Today”) or to the practices of any person or entity other than Egypt Today, including operators of websites you may visit before or after visiting the Site and the owners or publishers of the Publications you purchase, download or otherwise access through the Service.

**Information We Collect**

Egypt Today collects information from users, which may include personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”), at different points on the Site and through the Service or the Egypt Today Reader software as follows:

**Information You Give Us**

We receive and store information you enter on the Site or give us in any other way.

·  **Registration data:**  
When you register for the Service, we ask that you provide basic contact information such as your name, Cell (Mobile) Number, Gender, Birthday, address, and email address.

·  **Order data:**  
When you order Publications through the Service, we collect your purchase and address or billing information, including your credit card number and expiration date. :

·  **Voluntary information:**  
We may collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, change your content or email preferences, respond to a survey, or communicate with Egypt Today customer support.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via the Site.

·  **Computer and device configuration, identification and location:**  
We automatically receive and log information from your browser, including your IP address, the name and ID of your computer, mobile device and other devices, your operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, connection speed, and location information based on your IP address and as derived from GPS or similar features on your mobile device and other devices.

·  **Referral, clickstream, and site interaction data:**  
We may also record the URL you linked from to get to the Site, your clickstream through and from the Site, and other tracking information.

·  **Email delivery and open rates:**  
To help us make our emails more useful and interesting, and to ensure that we are delivering the Publications you have ordered, we often receive a confirmation when you receive and/or open email from Egypt Today. In addition, we collect offline readership information.

·  **Software installation, file downloads, and publication access:**  
When you install the Adobe Acrobat Reader software or download Publications or other files from the Site, we may record when each file transfer begins and ends and any errors that interrupt the transfer.

**Information from Other Sources**

**We may receive information abou** t you from other sources, add it to our account information and treat it in accordance with this Policy.

·  **Customer and order data from our partners:**  
If you place an order for a Publication directly with the publisher or another Egypt Today partner for which we provide fulfillment or another service, your account information and order information is passed to us.

·  **Updated delivery and address information:**  
We may obtain updated contact information from third parties in order to correct our records and fulfill your orders or deliver communications to you.

·  **Demographic and purchase information:**  
We may reference other sources of demographic and purchase information in order to provide you with more targeted communications and promotions.

**How We Use Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a website can store on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit the Site, create a user account, download or purchase a product from us, or sign-in to the Adobe Acrobat Reader software we may set cookies on your personal computer. We require that cookies be enabled in your Web browser so that we can identify you as a repeat visitor or customer and maintain session information for logged-in users. We also use cookies to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of the Site. Egypt Today may allow other companies that are providing content on the Site to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of cookies is subject to their respective privacy policies.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

**Egypt Today uses information about you to:**

· Deliver the Publications and other products you order or that are sent to you

· Verify access to secure content and your account information

· Determine whether you meet the minimum system requirements for use of the Service

· Provide you tailored content and instructions, renewal options and promotions

· Service your customer support requests

· Ask you to participate in surveys about our products and services

· Offer you Service upgrades

· Better understand, on an anonymous and aggregated basis, how the Service is being used, including Web traffic and reading patterns, so that we may continually improve our Service

See below for a description of Egypt Today’s practices regarding e-mail communications to our users and how to update your preferences with respect to such e-mail communications.

**How We Share the Information We Collect**

**We may share your Personal Information only as follows:**

·  **Publishers and partners:**  
Egypt Today may provide publishers, and other merchants for whom Egypt Today sells or distributes Publications or other products, with any Personal Information in connection with or as is necessary to fulfill your requests for their products, programs or services, or to satisfy other core business functions. In such instances, your Personal Information is governed by their respective privacy policies.

·  **Agents:**  
We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf such as fulfilling orders, sending email, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies or individuals will be provided access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions, but these companies and individuals have agreed or will agree to not use your Personal Information for other purposes.

·  **Protection of the Site and others:**  
We release account and other Personal Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Service, the Adobe Acrobat Reader License Agreement , or other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, or others.

·  **Business transfers:**  
Egypt Today may transfer Personal Information it collects in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all or most of the assets of Egypt Today related to the Site and/or the Service. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Egypt Today may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Policy.

·  **Trusted third parties:**  
With your consent, we will make your Personal Information (not including your credit card information) available to trusted third parties who offer products and services we think may be of interest to you so that you can receive information or opportunities related to those products and services. You may update your preference with regard to our sharing your Personal Information for this purpose in the “email preferences” in the “account settings” area of the Site. These third parties with whom we share your Personal Information may use your Personal Information in accordance with their own privacy policies.

·  **With your consent:**  
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice prior to our sharing your Personal Information with any third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share your Personal Information.

Egypt Today reserves the right to use and disclose anonymous information, including aggregate information derived from your Personal Information, to inform publishers, partners, and other interested parties as to the usage habits or characteristics of Egypt Today user base; and to serve any other business purposes.

Email Communications to our Users

Egypt Today does not send unsolicited email, but we do send email communications to our users in connection with the provision of the Service. The following outlines the types of email Egypt Today sends to our users and the choices you have about which messages to receive.

·  **Content Delivery messages:**

Egypt Today will send you email containing a download link for the content purchased or subscribed for on periodically based on the type of purchase.

·  **Messages required to service orders you place for Publications and products fulfilled by** Egypt Today **:**  
Egypt Today will send you email notifying you of the availability of each Publication or other product or service that you order either directly from Egypt Today or from one of our publisher or other merchant partners. ****

·  **Messages required to service your** Egypt Today **account:**  
Egypt Today may send you the following messages: (a) for newly registered users, a welcoming email;(b) messages confirming each order you place directly on the Site; (c) messages confirming your account changes; (d) messages inviting you to participate in customer surveys; and (e) messages informing you of important product or service updates related to our business.

·  **Marketing messages about Publications you receive:**  
We may send you marketing messages related to the Publications you receive including, for example, messages encouraging you to purchase additional single copies or to subscribe to Publications.

·  **Optional marketing messages from** Egypt Today **:**  
Registered users may also occasionally receive information or special promotions from Egypt Today about additional Publications, products or services. You may update your preference with regard to receiving such messages in the “email preferences” in the “account settings” area of the Site.

·  **Optional marketing messages from trusted third parties:**  
With your consent, Egypt Today may share your Personal Information (not including your credit card information) with trusted third parties so that you may receive information or opportunities from these third parties about relevant products and services they offer. You may update your preference in the “email preferences” in the “account settings” area of the Site.

**Changing or Removing Your Information**

To review or update your Personal Information, or to alter your email preferences, or preferences regarding how we share your Personal Information, go to “email preferences” in the “account settings” area of the Site.

If at any time you would like to close your account, send email to support@mediwave.me. Your Personal Information will be removed from our active user database and will be deleted, provided that (a) you are current with all payment obligations, (b) Egypt Today does not believe it reasonably necessary to keep such information for any pending legal action, and (c) we are under no obligation to retain such information. Please be aware that any unfulfilled subscriptions may be canceled without refund and you will have to re-register in order to use the Service. It is your responsibility to request a refund from Egypt Today or the appropriate merchant. ** **

**Security Practices**

Egypt Today uses commercially reasonable security methods to protect your Personal Information. Your Personal Information will be stored in a database located behind multiple firewalls and accessible only to authorized personnel. We do not encrypt normal Web sessions, but any transmission to our servers of credit card or other Personal Information uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Password and credit card information is stored in our database in an encrypted, non-human readable form.

**Children**

Egypt Today does not knowingly collect, either online or offline, Personal Information from persons under the age of thirteen.

**Notification of Changes**

From time to time, Egypt Today may revise this Policy. The update date first written above is used to alert you to recent changes. If changes to this Policy will directly affect how we share your Personal Information, we will notify you by posting a notice on the Site or by sending you an email and giving you an opportunity to opt out of such change. Unless we notify you otherwise, our collection and use of your Personal Information is governed by the version of this Policy in effect at the time such Personal Information is collected.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or our use of your information, please email support@mediwave.me or use the following address:  
Egypt Today 7 B, Road 199, Maadi, Cairo-Egypt

TERMS OF SERVICE

**Egypt Today Legal Notices**

Please review ET Terms of Service, and Refund Policy below.

· Terms of Service

· Refund Policy

**Terms of Service**  
Welcome to Egypt Today! Access to, and use of Egypt Today website located at egypttoday.com (the “Site”) and other Egypt Today Internet services (together with access to and use of the Site, the “Service” are subject to the following Terms of Service (these “Terms”). Please read these Terms carefully. Creating an account with Egypt Today or otherwise accessing or using the Service will signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by these Terms and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations. These Terms constitute a binding agreement between you and Egypt Today (“ET” or “we” or “our”). If you do not agree to these Terms, you may not use the Service.

THESE TERMS CONTAIN WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS AND OTHER PROVISIONS THAT LIMIT THE LIABILITY OF Egypt Today. PLEASE READ THESE TERMS IN THEIR ENTIRETY. ****

**1\. Description of Service**

The Service is operated by Egypt Today, and includes the Site through which you order, subscribe to and receive various digital magazines and other publications, content and products (collectively, the “Publications”). Use of the PDF Reader software is also subject to the [Adobe Acrobat License Agreement.](http://gb.zinio.com/legal/reader-license.jsp)

**2.Your Account**

Certain portions of the Service are available only to individuals who have registered with and obtained a password from Egypt Today. By registering with Egypt Today, you certify that you are at least 18 years of age. You may not provide or use a password, email address, or any other information of anyone else in connection with the Services. You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself when you register with or order Publications from Egypt Today, and to maintain and promptly update that information to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account, including the selection and use of all content and services.

**3\. User Conduct**

You may only use the Service for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms, any operating rules established by Egypt Today from time to time and the [Adobe Acrobat Reader License Agreement](http://gb.zinio.com/legal/reader-license.jsp). Egypt Today reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, or cancel orders at any time in its sole discretion, including, without limitation, based on any activity by a subscriber in violation of these Terms or applicable laws and regulations.

**4.International Users**

The Service is controlled, operated and administered by ePRESS from its offices and servers located within the United States of America. If you access the Service from a location outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all applicable local laws and regulations. You agree that you will not use the Service or any Publications accessed through the Service in any country or in any manner prohibited by the United States Export Administration Act or any other applicable laws or regulations.

**5\. Intellectual Property**

All content included as part of the Service, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, as well as compilations thereof, and all software used on the Site, is the property of Egypt Today or its suppliers or licensors, and is protected by Egypt and law, and applicable international laws and treaties, including without limitation copyright and other laws and treaties that protect intellectual property and proprietary rights. You agree to observe and abide by all such applicable laws and treaties, and to not alter, obscure or remove any copyright and other proprietary notices, legends (whether outlining restrictions on use or otherwise) contained in any such content.

Each third-party content provider owns the copyright in and to all content original to it, including without limitation on the Publications delivered or otherwise made available to you through the Service. Except as permitted by the Publication’s lawful owner, you acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights in a Publication by downloading a Publication accessed through the Service.

Except as explicitly required under applicable copyright laws and treaties or permitted by the features of the Service and Egypt Today Reader software, you may not modify, reverse engineer, publish, transmit, display, participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works of, or in any way commercially exploit or provide to a third party access to the content of the Site, the Publications, or any portion of them without the express permission of Egypt Today and the owner of such content.

We do not grant you any licenses, express or implied, to the intellectual property of Egypt Today or our licensors except as expressly authorized by these Terms or the [Adobe Acrobat Reader License Agreement.](http://gb.zinio.com/legal/reader-license.jsp)

**6\. Third-Party Content**

Egypt Today is a distributor (not a publisher) of the Publications. Accordingly, we have no editorial control over the Publications. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers or other information or content expressed or made available by third parties, including those made in Publications offered by the Service, are those of the respective author(s) or publisher(s) and not of Egypt Today. Egypt Today does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of all or any portion of any Publication or any services or offers made by third parties, nor will we be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information contained in any Publication, or your use of services offered, or your acceptance of any offers made through the Service or the Publications.

The Service may contain links to other Internet sites and third-party resources. Egypt Today does not assume any responsibility or liability for communications or materials available through such linked sites. These links are provided for your convenience only. You are solely responsible for understanding any terms and conditions that may apply when you visit or place an order for products or services through, or otherwise use a third-party site.

**7.Modifications to Service**

We reserve the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that Egypt Today shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Service.

**8.Disclaimer of Warranties**

THE SERVICE AND ALL PUBLICATIONS ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. Egypt Today, ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, LICENSORS AND AGENTS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER Egypt Today NOR ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, LICENSORS OR AGENTS, MAKES ANY WARRANTY THAT (A) THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (B) THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE, (C) THE INFORMATION THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SERVICE OR THAT MAY BE CONTAINTED IN THE PUBLICATIONS WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, OR (D) THE QUALITY OF ANY PUBLICATIONS OR THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.

YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBILE FOR OBTAINING AND MAINTAINING RELIABLE INTERNET CONNECTIVITY. Egypt Today IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR INABILITY TO DOWNLOAD OR OTHERWISE ACCESS CONTENT.

ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OR USE OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL.

NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM Egypt Today OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY.

**9.Limitation of Liability**

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER Egypt Today NOR ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS LICENSORS, OR AGENTS BE LIABLE UNDER ANY THEORY OF LAW, FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF Egypt Today FOR CLAIMS ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE OR PUBLICATIONS OR OTHERWISE SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE FEES PAID BY YOU TO Egypt Today FOR THE PORTION OF THE SERVICE OR PUBLICATION GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM.

**10\. Indemnification**

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Egypt Today, its licensors, suppliers and any third-party content providers and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against all claims, losses, expenses, damages and costs, including attorney’s fees, arising out of or resulting from (a) your use of the Service or the Publications, (b) your violation of these Terms, or (c) any activity related to your account (including negligent or wrongful conduct) by you or any other person accessing the Service or the Publications using your account.

**11\. Monitoring**

Egypt Today retains the right, but not the obligation, to monitor the Service to determine compliance with these Terms and any operating rules established by Egypt Today, and to satisfy any law, regulation or authorized government request. Without limiting the foregoing, we retain the right to remove any content that we, in our sole discretion, find to be in violation of the provisions hereof or otherwise objectionable or in breach of Egypt Today’s or its licensors’ obligations.

**12\. Termination**

Either Egypt Today or you may terminate these Terms at any time. Without limiting the foregoing, Egypt Today may, in its sole discretion and without liability, terminate your password, or use of the Service for any reason, including, without limitation, if Egypt Today believes that you have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of these Terms. Any termination of your access to the Service under any provision of these Terms may be effected without prior notice, and Egypt Today may immediately deactivate or delete your account and all related information and/or bar any further access to the Service. Sections 2, 4, 5, 6 and 8 through17 shall survive termination of these Terms.

**13\. Continuous Service Program**

All subscription orders will include “Continuous Service” which enables you to receive uninterrupted delivery of Publications until you cancel your subscriptions. You may cancel subscriptions at any time and receive a refund for any unserved issues (see Refund Policy below). With Continuous Service, after all issues of a Publication in your initial subscription period have been served, you will be billed automatically, at the end of your initial subscription period, for the next subscription period in accordance with the then-current offer terms applicable to that Publication as they appear on our Service.

**14\. Pricing and Tax**

All pricing featured on the Site is inclusive of VAT, GST and sales tax. Purchase transactions will include VAT, GST or sales tax based on your billing address and the tax rates in effect at the time your transaction is completed. Egypt Today will only charge tax in countries where digital goods are taxable. No customers are eligible for the tax exemptions for transactions made on the Service. All pricing and tax on the Egypt Today iPad and iPhone apps will follow Apple’s iTunes Terms and Conditions.

**15\. Miscellaneous**

These Terms, the [Adobe Acrobat Reader License Agreement](http://gb.zinio.com/legal/reader-license.jsp) and the other rules, guidelines, licenses and disclaimers posted on the Site constitute the entire agreement between Egypt Today and you with respect to your use of the Service and supersede all previous written or oral agreements between us with respect to the subject matter hereof. These Terms shall be governed by the statutes and laws of the Arab Republic of Egypt (A.R.E). No waiver by either party of any breach or default hereunder shall be deemed to be a waiver of any preceding or subsequent breach or default.

**16\. Notification of Changes**

From time to time, Egypt Today may revise these Terms to keep them up to date with Egypt Today’s products and services. Please refer to the Site periodically for any changes. The update date first written above is used to alert you to recent modifications. Your access or use of the Service subsequent to such an update will signify your assent to be bound by such changes

**17\. Our Address**

MediaWave

7B, Road 199, Maadi, Cairo-Egypt

**Refund Policy**

1\. Refund policy for credit card purchases on egypttoday.com

Egypt Today will provide a refund for all unserved issues of Publications to the original credit card used for purchase. Single copy purchases will only be refunded in the event that you are unable to download the issue. Please go to Egypt Today’s help page to request a refund.

_Last updated October, 2015_
